<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="22910">
		<path>./Time Crisis - Crisis Zone (USA).gz</path>
		<name>Time Crisis : Crisis Zone</name>
		<desc>This third Time Crisis game designed for PlayStation 2 sets the light-gun shooter action in a busy commercial district in the suburbs of London. A group of terrorists has taken over a building, but little else is known of their true purpose, as the player's crack shot hero arrives at the scene with orders to liberate the market square and resolve the situation by any means necessary.
 Crisis Zone for the PlayStation 2 is a port of the arcade game of the same name, and it is a spin-off from the Time Crisis series. In the game you are part of an elite anti-terrorist group called Special Tactical Force and you are sent to fight a terrorist group called U.R.D.A. The terrorist group has taken over an office center and wants to destroy the nuclear reactor buried deep beneath the complex. It's up to you, to stop them.</desc>
		<image>./images/Time Crisis - Crisis Zone (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Time Crisis - Crisis Zone (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Time Crisis - Crisis Zone (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Time Crisis - Crisis Zone (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20041019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220720T100704</lastplayed>
		<gametime>236</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="22549">
		<path>./Time Crisis 3 (USA).gz</path>
		<name>Time Crisis 3</name>
		<desc>The third installment in Namco's light gun shooting franchise, Time Crisis 3 offers exciting, fast-paced shooting action by the world renowned VSSE agents as they fight to save an innocent nation from total annihilation. Choose from four weapons--machine gun, handgun, shotgun, and grenade-- to blast your way past enemies. Practice your sharpshooting skills in Sniper Combat and multiple gameplay modes. The game also includes multiple gameplay modes, a new playable character, and the original Time Crisis. It's time to warm up that trigger finger and step into the action.</desc>
		<image>./images/Time Crisis 3 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Time Crisis 3 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Time Crisis 3 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Time Crisis 3 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20031023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220720T100254</lastplayed>
		<gametime>184</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="22761">
		<path>./Time Crisis II (USA).gz</path>
		<name>Time Crisis II</name>
		<desc>Play alone or team up with a friend in this traditional light gun shooter.
Christy Ryan, the agent responsible for uncovering the corporation's hidden agenda, attempts to escape NDI captivity and report the details of the plot to V.S.S.E. HQ, but is captured by Jakov Kinisky and his bodyguards. V.S.S.E. sends agents Keith Martin and Robert Baxter to shut down the Starline Network and rescue Ryan.</desc>
		<image>./images/Time Crisis II (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Time Crisis II (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Time Crisis II (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Time Crisis II (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Time Crisis II (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>43</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220723T131037</lastplayed>
		<gametime>1948</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="23199">
		<path>./Ninja Assault (USA).bin</path>
		<name>Ninja Assault</name>
		<desc>An enhanced port of Namco's 2000 coin-op game, Ninja Assault comes to PlayStation 2 with support for the Guncon 2 peripheral and new modes of play. A wicked Shogun named Kigai, with the help of a demonic army, invaded the peaceful land of Tenshin, butchered the royal family, and made off with Princess Koto. Determined to get their beloved ruler back, ninjas Guren and Gunjo plan on challenging the army with little more than their wits, the power of Ninjutsu magic, and deadly Mach Guns. A young girl named Aoi also wants to see Kigai pay, and plans on joining them as they enter the heart of enemy territory.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ninja Assault (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ninja Assault (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ninja Assault (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ninja Assault (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20021119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>23</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220908T182640</lastplayed>
		<gametime>762</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="22763">
		<path>./Vampire Night (USA).gz</path>
		<name>Vampire Night</name>
		<desc>Vampire Night is a light gun game produced by Sega's Wow Entertainment, distributed through Namco and released in 2000 for video game arcades. It was later ported to PlayStation 2 in November 2001. Two players can team up to take down on screen enemies.

A struggle between light and dark, from 300 years back, is about to ensue. The parties involved are Michel and Albert, the two vampire hunters representing light, and the vampires representing dark. The story takes place in an alternate version of the year 2006 in France, when progress looks stuck in the late 19th century.

Michel and Albert rescue a 12-year-old girl named Caroline who witnessed a couple of villagers held hostage by the vampire sarcoma. After rescuing the villagers and Caroline, the vampire hunters proceed into the castle to destroy the remaining forces of dark.

Although the forces of evil reveal that they created Michel and Albert to kill themselves, they became afraid of death and tried to stop them. It is important to note the Hunters are in fact Dhampyrs (half-vampires), foreshadowed by their glowing eyes and sunglasses. The outcome is a pyrrhic victory for the forces of good; as the forces of evil are stopped, the Vampire Hunters decide to let the rising sun end their own lives as well.

The game ends with Caroline paying her respects to the Vampire Hunters at their graves.</desc>
		<image>./images/Vampire Night (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Vampire Night (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Vampire Night (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Vampire Night (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T180000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220720T100855</lastplayed>
		<gametime>105</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
</gameList>
